Sujith Srinivas

Order to cash operations associate.

Address: #54, 20th Main, RK Layout, Near Maharaja Agrasen Hospital, Bengaluru, Karnataka, India, 560070

Phone: (+91) 8123930427

Email: sujithreddyaug1998@gmail.com

Four years of corporate order and cash management experience have been gained, with proficiency demonstrated in Excel, VBA, and other Microsoft Office applications. Strong analytical, reporting, and organizational skills have been applied, along with a proven record in customer service and dispute management. Knowledge has been acquired in ETL processes, dashboard creation, and Power Platform tools, including Power Automate (Cloud & Desktop), Power Apps, and Power BI.

Professional Experience

Accenture PLC.

April 2022 - Present

Order to cash operations associate.

Dispute Management:

- Analyzed, researched, and resolved payment claims within required timeframes.
- Raising dispute case for unsatisfied customer and validate team.
- Identifying the disputes and categorizing under different reason codes on daily basis. And assess the cause for the error and devise a plan or use of technology to mitigate it.
- Closely work with Credits, Sales, Order management, Cash Applications, Legal and License Migration teams to resolve booking and invoicing related issues.
- Following up with customer for details to solve the query. Validating the deductions and assigning to market for further a validation
- Check if the invoices are billed as per the correct payment terms agreed in the contract if not amend and issue a new invoice with correct payment terms,
- Monitored the Electronic data interchange and identified the future errors which customers might face and did a work around to avoid the nonpayment of invoices.
- Created many automation scripts such as Auto reminder after every 5 days using power automate. Creation of Credit memo and debit memo referring to the source documents using VBA and SAP GUI scripting. A VBA user-form control was introduced due to inefficiency in the use of a checklist, which in later provided a better interface and was user friendly.

Maintec Technologies Pvt Ltd

March 2021 - April 2022

Transaction processing Associate

Deployed to Accenture on a contract basis.

Order Management:

- Handling Invoice processing PO.
- Prepared Daily production report Of SAP entity. Handled Review Queue,

- Monitor and resolve order and interface issues.
- Ensuring all day-to-day and monthly activities is completed.
- Execution Of operational metrics and SLA reporting
- Liaise with internal contacts including sales and marketing, logistics, distribution.

Cash Application:

- Applying for the received payment in the SAP ERP
- Handling the Cash application payment such as Bank Transfers, Cheque Payment, etc. Handling email and escalation from the client.
- Contact Market authority for information relating to unapplied payments by follow-up on open item and un-applied payment.
- Explore continuous process improvement areas and share best practices across teams.
- Perform and ensure Quality checks for various country codes in Cash application processes, as per the agreed criteria.

Education

Cost And Management Accountant (Inter) January 2020 - December 2020 ICMAI at Bangalore

Expertise knowledge in Accounts and Taxation, with a focus on financial analysis, taxation, and accounting principles. Possess a comprehensive understanding of corporate financial and taxation regulations, as well as the ability to prepare accurate and timely financial reports, Adept at using financial software to create reports, analyze financial data, and project future financial trends. Skilled at working with internal and external stakeholders to ensure accurate financial records. Possess strong problem-solving, analytical, and communication skills.

Bachelors in commerce June 2016 - April 2019 **Bangalore University at Bangalore**

Expertise knowledge in Accounts and Taxation, with a focus on financial analysis, taxation, and accounting principles. Possess a comprehensive understanding of corporate financial and taxation regulations, as well as the ability to prepare accurate and timely financial reports, Adept at using financial software to create reports, analyze financial data, and project future financial trends. Skilled at working with internal and external stakeholders to ensure accurate financial records. Possess strong problem-solving, analytical, and communication skills.

Key Skills

- Customer service, Problem Solving, Communication skills.
- Microsoft office products, VBA, Macros. Cloud Automation
- Reporting, Analytics
- Communication skills
- Time management

Hobbies

Sports

Reading, Trading and Investing

Acknowledgement

I hereby confirm that all the facts stated above are accurate to the best of my belief.